{
    "kind": "Unscramble",
    "questions": [
        {
            "Nomenclatura": "WBP1M1L3d.json",
            "kind": "Unscramble",
            "Instruccion": "Unscramble the letters to make words.",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "e / f / o / c / i / f",
                    "answer": "office"
                },
                {
                    "question": "t / m / a / o / h / o / b / r",
                    "answer": "bathroom"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "Nomenclatura": "WBP1M1L4a.json",
            "kind": "Unscramble",
            "Instruccion": "Unscramble the commands",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Up / Stand",
                    "answer": "Stand up"
                },
                {
                    "question": "please / down / Sit",
                    "answer": "Sit down please"
                },
                {
                    "question": "your / Open / notebook",
                    "answer": "Open your notebook"
                },
                {
                    "question": "a song / Sing",
                    "answer": "Sing a song"
                },
                {
                    "question": "trumpet / Play / the",
                    "answer": "Play the trumpet."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "Nomenclatura": "WBP1M3L14a.json",
            "kind": "Unscramble",
            "Instruccion": "Unscramble the questions.",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "in the ocean / live / rats / Do / ?",
                    "answer": "Do rats live in the ocean?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "in the jungle / Do / live / ? / camels",
                    "answer": "Do camels live in the jungle?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "camels / ? / in the desert / Do / live ",
                    "answer": "Do camels live in the desert?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "sharks / ? / in the ocean / Do / live",
                    "answer": "Do sharks live in the ocean?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "chimpanzees / ? / live / Do / on the plain",
                    "answer": "Do chimpanzees live on the plain?"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "Nomenclatura": "WBP1M3L14c.json",
            "kind": "Unscramble",
            "Instruccion": "Unscramble the words",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "rkash",
                    "answer": "shark"
                },
                {
                    "question": "atr",
                    "answer": "rat"
                },
                {
                    "question": "macle",
                    "answer": "camel"
                },
                {
                    "question": "pholind",
                    "answer": "dolphin"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "Nomenclatura": "WBP1M4L20b.json",
            "kind": "Unscramble",
            "Instruccion": "Unscramble the sentences",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "you / ? / ride / Can / a bicycle",
                    "answer": "Can you ride a bicycle? "
                },
                {
                    "question": "a bicycle / ? / have / Does / three wheels",
                    "answer": "Does a bicycle have three wheels? "
                },
                {
                    "question": "any / Are / taxis / ? / there / in your neighborhood ",
                    "answer": "Are there any taxis in your neighbourhood? "
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}